# HAESUNG LEE

IOT DATA SW ENGINEER

2/10 Orwell St, Potts Point, NSW, 2011 (Crafted GPS Map)

### Download PDF

achasma@gmail.com +61432399841

My Tech Tutorial Blog||Twitter||Facebook My Skill Chart

My GitHub

### **PROFILE**

I am a keen IoT inventor as a hobbyist in Sydney and very passionate about IoT and Alogrithms such as MACHINE LEARNING, COMPUTATIONAL STATISTICS and so on. Also, I have spent almost every day of the past 15 years making robots or electronic inventions or computer programs.

SUMMARY OF MY **SKILLS** 

**Web Programing** 

Junior Level

IoT HW & SW

Data Science

Mid Level

Mid - Senior Level

### SKILL. **CHART**

- Full-Stack
- Data Science
- My Skill Chart

HTML	IBM NodeRED	R
CSS	C & C++	Machine Learning
JavaScript	GPS & Sensors & PCB	GNU Octave
IBM Cloud Bluemix	Twillo(Phone Message)	Matlab
Linux	Arduino & Raspberry Pi	IBM Cloudant NoSQL
Python	Wireless & MQTT	IBM Apache Spark
Node.js	IBM Watson IoT	Computational Stat

### **EXPERIENCE**

- Open Source
- Meetup - MOOC
- Leadership - Volunteer
- Startup
- Developer
- Engineer
- Portfolio Box - Certificate Box

## Personal Sotware Acitivities, Sydney

2013-2016

**Open Source Communities:** 

IBM Node-RED||Twilio Python||IBM IoT Python||Python Sense Hat||Data Science Python||IBM NoSQL

Python | Python Twitter

**MEETUPs:** 

OzBerry IoT||Sydney IoT||Sydney Python||Big Data Analytics

A Developer's Guide to the IoT by IBM | Statistical Learning(Stanford University)

Machine Learning(Stanford University)||The Data Scientist's Toolbox(Johns Hopkins University)

TEAM LEADERSHIP:

Term 1: Developing the Leader Within You(Hillsong Leadership Evening College) Term 2: Developing the Leaders Around You(Hillsong Leadership Evening College)

Australia Salvation Army | IBM Open Source Helper | Hillsong City Care

## **AKASMA**, South Korea

2010-2011

- Designed a recycling can system to refund a electronic money.
- The prodcut name was called "Green Can-Money Sysetm".
- Faild my own business for marketting and getting fund.

**CAS Electronics**, South Korea **Junior Product Developer** 

2007-2009

- Developed firmware(C&C++) of products: Weighing Controller & Indicator.
- Improved failure rate of production from 30% to 2% by factor of PB.

### Honewell Korea(JaCC Engineering)

2003-2007

Junior Installment Engineer

- Installed & programmed FA Controllers such as PLC, SCADA, DCS.

### **EDUCATION**

- IT School
- English School
- Bachelor
- Certificate Box

### Sydney College of Business and IT, Sydney

2015-2017

- Learned HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL,

Visual Basic.net, Visual C++, C#,

Software Testing & Deployment and Copyright Ethics.

### Stepone Language College, Sydeny

2012-2014

- Improved my English Skills such as Grammar, Writing, Speaking, English Conversation and Aussie Accent.

- Had a working holiday experience to improve my English Skill.

# <u>Seoul National University of Technology</u>, South Korea <u>Bachelor</u> of Control and Instrumentation Engineering (4.0 GPA)

2007-2009

- Learned C Programing, Intelligent Control(Fuzzy Control), Modern Control(Neural

- Learned C Programing, Intelligent Control(Fuzzy Control), Modern Control(Neural Network), Automatic Control(PID), Digital Signal Processing, Electronic & Electric design.
- Invented a patent of Oxygen generator for soil (Korea Pat: 10-0734438)
- Awarded Korea Ministry Award of Oxygen Generator System for soil

Haesung Lee - achasma@gmail.com - +61432399841